Sometimes love is hiding between the seconds of your life.
Cashback is a drama, comedy, romance film directed by Sean Ellis.
After a painful breakup, Ben develops insomnia.
To kill time, he starts working the late night shift at the local
supermarket, where his artistic imagination runs wild.
Ben Willis, played by Sean Biggerstaff.
Sharon Pintey, played by Emilia Fox.
Sean Higgins, played by Shaun Evans.
Barry Brickman, played by Michael Dixon.
Suzy, played by Michelle Ryan.
Jenkins, played by Stuart Goodwin.
Cashback is a 2006 British romantic comedy-drama film
written and directed by Sean Ellis.
Originally exhibited as a short in 2004, it was
expanded to feature length in 2006.
Both versions were produced by Lene Bausager,
starring Sean Biggerstaff and Emilia Fox.
The film explores themes of night shift, london,
england, supermarket, boredom, painting.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.